(Beverley:)-Did I thank you for the flowers?
-You did.
(Beverley:)-I don't really like flowers.
-Neither do I.
(Sheldon:)-But it's the social convention.
-It is, isn't it?
(Leonard:)Wait, wait, wait. You had surgery?
(Beverley:)-Yes, and Sheldon sent me flowers.
-No, I heard that.
(Beverley:)Then what was all that
"wait, wait, wait" about?
(Leonard:)I just don't understand why
he knows more about your life than I do.
(Beverley:)Because Sheldon and I stay in touch
due to mutual interest and respect...
(Beverley:)...while you avoid me
due to unresolved childhood issues.
(Sheldon:)It's what we think caused
your narcissistic-personality disorder.
(Sheldon:)We discussed it at length
during our last video chat.
(Sheldon:)Although how we got
onto the subject of you is baffling.
(Beverley:)Yes, but we are on the subject,
so I'm obliged to ask.
(Beverley:)Leonard, how are you?
(Leonard:)-Fine, Mom. How are you?
-Menopausal.
(Leonard:)Now I'm less fine.
-Have you heard your brother's engaged?
-No.